Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series C: General Archives
  - Subseries 4: Financial Information
    - Financial Information-Proposed Budget, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Financial Information-Pledge Drive, 11/1987 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1-6/1987 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 7-12/1987 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Financial Information-Report-End of Year, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Financial Information-Report-9 Month, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Financial Information-Report-6 Month, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Financial Information-Report-3 Month, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Financial Information-Proposed Budget, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Financial Information-Pledge Drive, 11/1988 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Financial Information-Receipt Book (Funds Received) 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1-6/1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 7-12/1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers-1/1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers-2/1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers-3/1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers-4/1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers-5/1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Vouchers-6/1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Vouchers-7/1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Vouchers-8/1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Vouchers-9/1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Vouchers-10/1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Vouchers-11/1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Vouchers-12/1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements, 1-6/1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements, 7-12/1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1-6/1989 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 7-12/1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Financial Information-Cash Receipts, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Financial Information-Proposed Budget, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Financial Information-Report-3/1989 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Financial Information-Report-9/1989 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Financial Information-Report-End of Year, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Financial Information-Pledge Drive, 11/1989 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Financial Information-Payroll Records, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks-12/14/1989-1/15/1990, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks-3/14-5/13 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks-8/15-11/14 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks-11/15/1990-1/14/1991, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1-6/1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 7-12/1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers-1/1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Vouchers-2/1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Vouchers-3/1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Vouchers-4/1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Vouchers-5/1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Vouchers-6/1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Vouchers-7/1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Vouchers-8/1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Vouchers-9/1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers-10/1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers-11/1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers-12/1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 3/22-12/13 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Financial Information-Events Checking Account, 7-12/1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Financial Information-Cash Receipts, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Financial Information-Proposed Budget, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Financial Information-Payroll Records, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Financial Information-Report-3 Month, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 1/15-7/14 1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 7/15-12/12/1991 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 1/15/1991-1/14/1992, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Financial Information-Cash Receipts, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Vouchers-1/1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Vouchers-2/1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Vouchers-3/1991 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Vouchers-4/1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers-5/1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers-6/1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers-7/1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers-8/1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers-9/1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers-10/1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Vouchers-11/1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Vouchers-12/1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Financial Information-Payroll, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 1-6/1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 7-9/1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 10-12/1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Financial Information-Cash Receipts, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 12/31/1991-6/11/1992, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 6/12-12/14 1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 1-6/1992 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Financial Information-Check Stubs, 7-12/1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Vouchers-1/1992 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers-2/1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers-3/1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers-4/1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers-5/1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers-6/1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers-7/1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Vouchers-8/1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Vouchers-9/1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Vouchers-10/1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Vouchers-11/1992 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Vouchers-12/1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Financial Information-Payroll, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Financial Information-Documents from Howard Moody's Financial Folder, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Financial Information-Reports, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Financial Information-Benevolences, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Financial Information-Cash Receipts, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 1-6/1993 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Financial Information-Bank Statements/Cancelled Checks, 7-12/1993 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Vouchers-1/1993 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Vouchers-2/1993 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Vouchers-3/1993 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Vouchers-4/1993 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Vouchers-5/1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Vouchers-6/1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers-7/1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Vouchers-8/1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers-9/1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers-10/1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Vouchers-11/1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Vouchers-12/1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 1-3/1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 4-6/1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Financial Information-Centennial Checking Account, 7-12/1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Financial Information-Payroll, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee-Capital Funds Committee, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Finance Committee-Reports, 1983-86, 1983-1986 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Finance Committee-1987-92, 1987-1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Finance Committee-Investment Subcommittee Endowment, 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Finance Committee-Pledge Dinner, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Finance Committee-Investment Subcommittee Endowment, 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Finance Committee-Quarterly Financial Reports, 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Finance Committee-Minutes, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Finance Committee-Pledge Drive, 1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Finance Committee-Investment Subcommittee, 1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Finance Committee-Investment Subcommittee, 1991-92 [cont.], 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Subseries 5: Committees
    - Arts Advisory Committee-Religious Art Conference, 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Arts-Theater Evaluation Committee, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Arts-Theater Evaluation Committee, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Arts-Theater Evaluation Committee, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Arts-(Interim) Arts Committee, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Arts-Ad Hoc Committee for the Arts, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Arts-(Interim) Arts Committee-Minutes, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Arts Advisory Committee-1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Arts Advisory Committee-1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Arts Advisory Committee-1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Church Board-Annual Report (including resolution that Baptist City Mission Society take over property) 11/8/1912 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Church Board-Notes, 1929, 1936-37, 1929, 1936-1937 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Church Board-Annual Reports, 1940-41, 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Church Board-Deacons Meetings, 1942-46, 1942-1946 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Church Board-Deacons Meeting and Crusade Committee, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1947-49, 1947-1949 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-Minutes, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Church Board-Judson Council- 1950 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Church Board-Judson Council- 1951 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1952 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1953 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1954 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1955 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Church Board-Judson Council-1956 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Church Board-1957 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Church Board-1958 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Church Board-1959 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Church Board-1960 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Church Board-Advisory Council for Judson Church, 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Church Board Meeting-Servicing the Revolutions, 7/27/1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Church Board-Material for All-Day Board Meeting, 1/7/1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 9/17/1977 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 1/28/1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 9/16/1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 1/13/1979 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 1/13/1980 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1981 [cont.] (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Church Board-Small Group Meeting concerning Al Carmines' Resignation, 5/1981 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Church Board-Letter from Miriam Corbett, 6/18/1981 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Church Board-Details on Small Group Meetings, 7/21/1981 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Church Board-Report to Board, 10/5/1981 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Church Board-Holly Bean's Letter to Church Board concerning Lee Hancock, 12/30/1981 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 9/8/1982 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Church Board-Moderator's Letter to Chairpersons, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Church Board-Board of Trustees Roster, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Church Board-All-Day Joint Board Meeting, 1/15/1983 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Church Board-Board of Trustees Roster, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Church Board-Board of Trustees Roster, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Mailings, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Church Board-Summary of Minutes, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Church Board-All-Day Board Meeting, 8/24/1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Mailings, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Church Board-Summary of Minutes, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Summaries, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Mailings, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Church Board-Summary of Minutes, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Church Board-Minutes, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Mailings, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Church Board-Roster, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Mailings, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Meetings, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Meetings, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Meetings, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Church Board-Minutes and Meetings, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Congregational Meetings-1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Congregational Meetings- 1958 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Congregational Meetings- 1959 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Congregational Meetings-1960 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Congregational Meetings-1961 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Congregational Meetings-1962 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Congregational Meetings-1963 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Congregational Meetings-1964 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Congregational Meetings-1965 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Congregational Meetings-1967 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Congregational Meetings-1969 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Congregational Meetings-1970 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Congregational Meetings-1971 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Congregational Meetings-1972 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Congregational Meetings (re: change in by-laws) 1973 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Congregational Meetings-1974 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Congregational Meetings-1975 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Congregational Meetings-1977 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Congregational Meetings-1978 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Congregational Meetings-1979 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Congregational Meetings-1980 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Congregational Meetings-1981 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Congregational Meetings-1982 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Congregational Meetings-1983 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Congregational Meetings-1984 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Congregational Meetings (re: Central America and Cancer Help) 1985 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Congregational Meetings-1986 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Congregational Meetings-1987 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Congregational Meetings-1988 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Congregational Meetings-1989 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Congregational Meetings-1990-94, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Covenant, 3/1960 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1977 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1978 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Volunteer Survey, 9/1978 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1979 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Survey 5/1979 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Survey 5/1979 [cont.] (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Roster, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Skill/Interest Survey, 4/1985 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1986 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Questionnaire Part I, Fall 1986 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Questionnaire Part II, Fall 1986 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Questionnaire, Tally and Analysis, Fall 1986 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1987 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1989-92, 1989-1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Congregational Life Committee-1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Congregational Life Committee-Congregation Dinners 10/18/1994 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - General-Memorial Committee Agreement, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - General-Committee Reports, 1923-25, 1923-1925 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - General-Foundation Request for Self-Study (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - General-Committee/Skills Questionnaire (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - General-Church Committees (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - General-Church Committees, 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - General-Church Committees, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - General-Church Committees, 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - General-Church Committees, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - General-Church Committees, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - General-Church Committees, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - General-Church Committees, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - General-Church Committees, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - General-Church Committees, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - General-Church Committees, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - General-Church Committees, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - General-Misc. Committee Notes, 1987-92, 1987-1992 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - General-Church Constitution and Charter, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous-Archives Committee, 1984, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous-Arts Archives Committee, 1976, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous-Audio-Visual Committee, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous-Communication Committee, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous-Kids Information Center Committee, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous-Membership and Voting Committee, 1975, 1978-79, 1975, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous-Music Committee, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous-Music Committee, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous-Nurture Commission, 1960 (1963-64), 1960-1964 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous-Pulpit Committee, 1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous-Search Committee, 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous-Song Book Committee, 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous-West Side Committee, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Nominating Committee-Minutes, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Nominating Committee-Nominee Letters, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Nominating Committee-for 1977 Church Board, 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Nominating Committee-1978 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Nominating Committee-1979 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Nominating Committee-1980 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Nominating Committee-1981 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Nominating Committee-1982 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Nominating Committee-1983 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Nominating Committee-1984 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Nominating Committee-1985 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Nominating Committee-1986 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Nominating Committee-1987 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Nominating Committee-1988 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Nominating Committee-1989 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Nominating Committee-1990 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Nominating Committee-1991 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Nominating Committee-1992 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Nominating Committee-1993 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Ordination Committee-1939-42, 1939-1942 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Ordination Committee-1950's (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Ordination Committee-1960's (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Ordination Committee-1970's (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Ordination Committee-1980's (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Ordination Committee-Adams, Nancy (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Ordination Committee-Collins, Clarence 1980 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Ordination Committee-1990-93, 1990-1993 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Ordination Committee-[no date] (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Personnel Committee-Job Descriptions, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - Personnel Committee-Minutes, 1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - Personnel Committee-1966, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - Personnel Committee-1972-79, 1972-1979 (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - Personnel Committee-1980-87, 1980-1987 (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - Personnel Committee-1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Committee-Procedural Report to Judson Board, 1/11/1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Committee-Warren Zeh Staff, 1990-92, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Committee-1990-94, 1990-1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1962-67, 1962-1967 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Social Concerns Committee-Corporate Responsibility, 1978-80, 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1980 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1981 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1982 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1984 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Social Concerns Committee-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)